Renaissance Architecture Lantern Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Italy (Box 68)
  - Lago Maggiore (Box 86)
  - Lecce (Box 86)
  - Legnago (Box 86)
  - Livorno (Box 86)
  - Lodi (Box 86)
  - Lonedo (Box 86)
  - Loreto (Box 86)
  - Lucca (Box 86)
    - Palace Bernadini (Box 86)
    - Palace Cenami (Box 86)
    - Palace Controni (Box 86)
    - Palace Manzi (Box 86)
    - Palace Provinciale (Box 86)
  - Macerata (Box 86)
  - Mantua (Box 86)
    - Churches (Box 86)
      - Cathedral (Box 86)
      - S. Andrea (Box 86)
      - S. Sebastiano (Box 86)
    - Palaces (Box 86)
      - Palazzo Ducale (Box 86)
      - Casa Giulio Romano (Box 87)
      - Palazzo Della Giustizia (Box 87)
      - Palazzo del Te (Box 87)
        - Exterior (Box 87)
        - Interior (Box 87)
      - Palazzo Vecchio (Box 87)
  - Maser (Box 87)
    - Villas (Box 87)
      - Villa Barbaro (Box 87)
        - Exterior (Box 87)
        - Interior (Box 87)
        - Tempietto (Box 87)
  - Messina (Box 87)
  - Milan (Box 87)
    - Churches (Box 87)
      - Cathedral (Box 87)
      - S. Alessandro (Box 87)
      - S. Ambrogio (Box 87)
      - S. Eustorgio (Chapel of S. Peter Martaire) (Box 87)
      - S. Fidele (Box 87)
      - S. Giusepe (Box 87)
      - S. Lorenzo (Box 87)
      - S. Maria Presso, S. Satiro (Box 87–88)
        - Exterior (Box 88)
        - Interior (Box 88)
      - S. Maria Della Grazie (Box 88)
        - Exterior (Box 88)
        - Interior (Box 88)
      - S. Maria Della Passione (Box 88)
      - S. Paolo (Box 88)
      - S. Satiro (Box 88)
        General
        Xx See S. Maria Presse, S. Satiro
    - Hospitals (Box 88)
      - Ospedale Maggiore (Box 88)
    - Museums (Box 88)
    - Palaces (Box 88)
      - Palace Delie Antiche Scuole (Box 88)
      - Palace Giuneconsulti (Box 88)
      - Palace Marino (Box 88)
      - Palace Degli Omensoni (Box 88)
      - Palace Serbelloni-Busca (Box 88)
    - Theaters (Box 88)
    - Villas (Box 88)
  - Mira (Box 88)
    - Villa Foscari (Box 88–89)
  - Mondovi (Box 89)
  - Mongiovino (Box 89)
  - Montagnana (Box 89)
  - Monte Cassino (Box 89)
  - Montecchio Precalcino (Box 89)
  - Montefiascone (Box 89)
  - Montepulciano (Box 89)
    - Churches (Box 89)
      - Cathedral (Box 89)
      - Chapel House (Box 89)
      - Madonna de S. Biagio (Box 89)
    - Fountains (Box 89)
    - Palaces (Box 89)
      - Palace Avignonesi (Box 89)
      - Palace Tamgi (Box 89)
  - Monte S. Angelo (Box 89)
  - Monza (Box 89)
  - Naples (Box 89)
    - Churches (Box 89)
      - Cathedral (Box 89)
      - Certosa di S. Martino (Monastery) (Box 89)
      - Chiara (Box 89)
      - Chiesa dell' Annunziata (Box 89–90)
      - Chiesa del Gesu Nuovo (Box 90)
      - Chiesa di Monteoliveto (Box 90)
      - Agostino Maggiore (Box 90)
      - Filippo Neri (Gerolomini) (Box 90)
      - Cappella Sanseverino & Sossic (Box 90)
      - S. Giovanni a Carbonara (Box 90)
    - Gates (Box 90)
      - Porta Capuana (Box 90)
    - Hospitals (Box 90)
      - Home for the Poor (Box 90)
    - Palaces (Box 90)
      - Castel Nuovo (Box 90)
      - Palazzo di Capodimonte (Box 90)
      - Palazzo Gravina (Box 90)
      - Palazzo Reale (Box 90)
    - Theaters (Box 90)
    - Villas (Box 90)
      - Poggioreale (Box 90)
  - Orvieto (Box 90)
  - Orzinuovi (Box 90)
  - Ostia (Box 90)
  - Padua (Box 90)
    - Churches (Box 90)
      - Cathedral (Box 90)
    - Schools (Box 90)
      - Universities (Box 90)
  - Palermo (Box 90)
  - Palmanova (Box 90)
  - Parma (Box 90)
    - Churches (Box 91)
      - Madonna Della Steccata (Box 91)
    - Theaters (Box 91)
  - Pavia (Box 91)
    - Churches (Box 91)
      - Cathedral (Box 91)
        - Exterior (Box 92)
        - Interior (Box 92)
      - Certosa (Box 92)
    - Palace Mezzabarba (Box 92)
  - Perugia (Box 92)
    - Churches (Box 92)
      - Madonna Della Luca (Box 92)
      - SS. Andres E. Bernadino (Box 92)
    - Gates (Box 92)
  - Pesaro (Box 92)
  - Pescia (Box 92)
  - Piacenza (Box 92)
    - Palace Farnese (Box 92)
  - Pienza (Box 92)
    - Churches (Box 92)
      - Cathedral (Box 92)
        - Exterior (Box 92)
        - Interior (Box 92)
    - Palaces (Box 92)
      - Palazzo Del Commune (Box 92)
      - Palazzo Piccolomini (Box 92)
        - Exterior (Box 92)
          - Court (Box 92)
        - Interior (Box 92)
      - Palazzo Vescovile (Box 92)
    - Squares (Box 92)
  - Piombino Dese (Box 92)
  - Pisa (Box 92)
    - Churches (Box 92)
      - Camposanto (Box 92)
    - Palaces (Box 92)
  - Pistoia (Box 92)
    - Churches (Box 92)
      - Madonna of Humility (Box 92)
      - Maria Della Grazia (Box 92)
    - Hospitals (Box 92)
      - Ospedale del Ceppo (Box 92)
  - Poggia a Caiano (Box 92)
    - Villas (Box 92)
      - Villa Medici (Box 92)
        - Exterior (Box 93)
  - Poiana Maggiore (Box 93)
  - Poppi (Box 93)
  - Prato (Box 93)
    - Madonna Della Carceri (Box 93)
  - Ragusa (Box 93)
  - Rieti (Box 93)
  - Rimini (Box 93)
    - San Francisco (Box 93)
      - Exterior (Box 93)
        - After Bombardment (Box 93)
        - During Reconstruction (Box 93)
          - Interior (Box 93)
  - Rome (Box 93)
    - Plans (Box 93)
      - 1534-38, from Mantua (Box 94)
      - 1676, by Falda (Box 94)
      - Sixtus V Plan (Box 94)
      - 1748, by Nolli (Box 94)
    - Views (Box 94)
      - Various (Box 94)
      - Castel S. Angelo (Box 94)
    - Churches (Box 94)
      - Abbazia Della Tre Fontane (Box 94)
      - Banco Santo Spirito (Box 94)
      - Bolognetti Chapel (Box 94)
      - Collegio di Propaganda Fide (Box 94)
      - Collegio Romano (Box 94)
      - Seven (Pilgrimage) Churches (Box 94)
      - Il Gesu (Box 94)
        - Exterior (Box 94)
        - Interior (Box 95)
      - Gesu & Maria (Box 95)
      - Oratorio di S. Filippo Neri (Box 95)
      - S. Agnese (Box 95)
        - Exterior (Box 95)
        - Interior (Box 95)
      - Alessio (Box 95)
      - S. Andrea in Via Flaminia (Box 95)
      - S. Andrea al Quirinale (Box 95)
      - S. Andrea delle Fratte (Box 95)
      - S. Andrea della Valle (Box 95)
      - S. Anna Del Palafrenieri (Box 95)
      - S. Antonio Dei Portoghesi (Box 95)
      - SS. Apostoli (Box 95)
      - S. Atanasio De'Greci (Box 96)
      - S. Bernardo (Box 96)
      - SS. Bonifacio E Alessio (Box 96)
      - S. Carlo A'Catinari (Box 96)
      - S. Carlo al Corso (Box 96)
      - S. Carloalle Quattre Fontane (Box 96)
        - Exterior (Box 96)
        - Interior (Box 96)
      - S. Caterina dei Funari (Box 96)
      - S. Cecilia (Box 96)
      - S. Constanza (Box 96)
      - S. Croce in Gerusalemme (Box 96)
      - S. Domenico (Box 96)
      - S. Elegio degli Orefici (Box 96)
      - S. Francesco a Ripa (Box 96)
      - S. Francesco Romana (Box 96)
      - S. Giacomo degli Spagnuoli (now Sacro Cuore Piazza Navone) (Box 96)
      - S. Giovanni Di Dio (Box 96)
      - S. Giovanni dei Fiorentini (Box 96)
        - Plans & Sections (Box 96–97)
        - Exterior (Box 97)
        - Interior (Box 97)
      - S. Giovanni in Olio (Box 97)
      - S. Girolamo della Carita (Box 97)
      - S. Girolamo degli Schiavoni (Box 97)
      - S. Gregorio Al Celio (Box 97)
      - S. Ignazio (Box 97)
        - Exterior (Box 97)
        - Interior (Box 97)
      - S. Ivo della Sapienza (Box 97)
        - Exterior (Box 97)
        - Interior (Box 97)
      - S. John Lateran – S. Giovanni in Laterano (Box 97)
        - Exterior (Box 97)
        - Interior (Box 97)
      - S. Luca & Martino (Box 97)
      - S. Luigi (Box 97)
      - S. Marcello (Box 98)
      - S. Margherita in Trastevere (Box 98)
      - S. Maria Degli Angeli (Box 98)
      - S. Maria Dell' Anima (Box 98)
      - S. Maria in Campitelli (Box 98)
        - Exterior (Box 98)
        - Interior (Box 98)
      - S. Maria Della Consolazione (Box 98)
      - S. Maria di Loreto (Box 98)
      - S. Maria Maddalena (Box 98)
      - S. Maria Maggiore (Box 98)
        - Plans, Sections, Project Elevations (Box 98)
        - Exterior (Box 98)
        - Interior (Box 98)
          - Padine Chapel (Box 98)
          - S. Forza Chapel (Box 98)
      - S. Maria dei Miracoli (Box 98)
      - S. Maria Di Monserrato (Box 98)
      - S. Maria Al Monte (Box 98)
      - S. Maria di Monte Santo (Box 98)
      - S. Maria dell'Orazione e Monte (Box 98)
      - S. Maria DellOrto (Box 99)
      - S. Maria Della Pace (Box 99)
        - Exterior (Box 99)
        - Interior (Box 99)
      - S. Maria del Popolo (Box 99)
        - Exterior (Box 99)
        - Interior (Box 99)
      - S. Maria del Priorato (Box 99)
      - S. Maria in Traspontina (Box 99)
      - S. Maria in Trastevere (Box 99)
      - S. Maria De'Sette Dolori (Box 99)
      - S. Maria Sopra Minerva (Box 99)
      - S. Maria in Vallicella (Box 99)
      - S. Maria in Via Lata (Box 99)
      - S. Maria Della Vittoria (Box 99)
      - S. Paolo Alie Tre Fontane (Box 99)
      - S. Pasquale Babylon (Box 99)
      - S. Peter's (Box 99)
        - General (Box 99)
          - Drawings (including Prints) (Box 99–100)
          - Cross Sections (Box 100)
          - Elevations (Box 100)
          - Medals (Box 100)
          - Models (Box 100)
          - Plans (Box 100–101)
          - Vatican Library Frescoes (Box 101)
            - Air Views (Box 101)
            - Piazza (Box 101)
          - Colonnade (Box 101)
          - Fountain (Box 101)
          - View from Dome (Box 101)
            - Exterior (Box 101)
              - Façade (Box 101)
              - Details (Box 101)
              - Dome (Box 101)
            - Interior (Box 101–102)
              - Details (Box 102)
              - Baldacchino (Box 102)
              - Dome (Box 102)
          - S. Pietro in Montorio (Box 102)
            - Exterior (Box 102)
            - Interior (Box 102)
          - S. Pietro Vincole (Box 102)
          - SS. Quaranta Martini (Box 102)
          - S. Salvatore in Lauro (Box 102)
          - S. Rita (Box 102)
          - S. Sebastiano (Box 102)
          - Santo Spirito in Sassis (Box 102)
          - S. Susanna (Box 102)
          - S. Trinita dei Monte (Box 102)
          - S. Trinita dei Pelligrini (Box 102)
          - S. Vicenzo e Anatasio (Box 102)
          - Tre Magi (Box 102)
    - Fountains (Box 103)
      - Pauline Fountain (Box 103)
      - Fountain of the Tortoises (Box 103)
      - Fontana di Trevi (Box 103)
    - Gates (Box 103)
      - Porta Furba (Box 103)
      - Porta Pia (Box 103)
      - Porta del Popolo (Box 103)
    - Government Buildings (Box 103)
      - Customs House (Box 103)
    - Hospitals (Box 103)
    - Houses (Box 103)
    - Museums (Box 103)
    - Palaces (Box 103)
      - Palazzo Alberoni (Box 103)
      - Palazzo Altemps (Box 103)
      - Palazzo Altieri (Box 103)
      - Palazzo Barberini (Box 103)
        - Exterior (Box 103)
        - Interior (Box 103)
      - Palazzo Borghese (Box 103)
      - Palazzo del Branconio Dell'Aquile (Box 104)
      - Palazzo Brasch (Box 104)
      - Palazzo Cancelleria (Box 104)
        - Exterior (Box 104)
        - Interior (Box 104)
      - Palazzo Chigi (Box 104)
        - Colonna (Box 104)
        - Nal. Conservation (Box 104)
        - Della Consulta (Box 104)
      - Palazzo Doria Pamphili (Box 104)
      - Palazzo Farnese (Box 104)
        - Exterior (Box 104)
        - Interior (Box 104)
        - Courtyard (Box 104–105)
      - Palazzo Giraud (Box 105)
      - Palazzo del Grillo (Box 105)
      - Palazzo Jacopo (Box 105)
      - Palazzo Julius II (Box 105)
      - Palazzo Lateran (Box 105)
      - Palazzo Marescotti (Box 105)
      - Palazzo Massimo alle Colonne (Box 105)
      - Palazzo Mattei (Box 105)
      - Palazzo Di Montecitorio (Box 105)
      - Palazzo De Montecitorio (Box 105)
      - Palazzo del Museo Capitolino (Box 105)
      - Palazzo Negroni (Box 105)
      - Palazzo Odescalchi (Box 105)
      - Palazzo Propaganda Fide (Box 105)
      - Palazzo del Quirinale (Box 105)
      - Palazzo Pamphili (Box 106)
      - Palazzo Raphael (Box 106)
      - Palazzo Della Rovere (Box 106)
      - Palazzo Sachetti (Box 106)
      - Palace Sanatorio (Box 106)
      - Palazzo Spada (Box 106)
      - Palazzo Tribunale (Box 106)
      - Palazzo Vaticano (Box 106)
      - Palazzo Venezia (Box 106)
      - Palazzo Vidoni-Caffarelli (Box 106)
      - Palazzo Zuccari (Box 106)
    - Prisons (Box 106)
    - Squares and Piazzas (Box 106)
      - Piazza del Campidoglio (Box 106)
        - Plans & Sections (Box 106)
        - Air Views (Box 106)
        - General Views (Box 106–107)
        - Capitoline Museum (Box 107)
        - Colonnade for Pope Paul III (Box 107)
        - Palazzo dei Conservatori (Box 107)
        - Palazzo Senatorio (Box 107)
        - Statue of Marcus Aurelius (Box 107)
      - Piazza Campitelli (Box 107)
      - Piazza Colonna (Box 107)
      - Piazza Della Minerva (Box 107)
      - Piazza Navona (Box 107)
      - Piazza del Popolo (Box 107)
      - Piazza del Quirinale (Box 107)
      - Piazza S. Ignazio (Box 107)
      - Piazza Maria Della Pace (Box 107)
      - Piazza S. Pietro (Box 107)
      - Piazza di Spagna (Box 107)
  - Vatican (Box 107)
    - Plans (Box 107)
    - Specif Parts of Vatican (Box 107)
      - Belvedere (Box 107)
        - Projects (Box 107)
        - Plans (Box 108)
        - Elevations & Sections (Box 108)
        - Drawings, Prints (Box 108)
        - Exteriors (Box 108)
        - Interiors (Box 108)
      - Borgia Apts. (Box 108)
      - Casino of Pius IV (Villa Pia) (Box 108)
      - Cortile Di S. Damaso (Box 108)
      - Library (Box 108)
      - Gardens (Box 108)
      - Loggia of Raphael (Box 108)
      - Museum (Box 108)
      - Pauline Chapel (Box 108)
      - Scala Regia (Box 108–109)
      - Sistine Chapel (Box 109)
    - Villas (Box 109)
      - Villa Albani (Box 109)
      - Villa Aldobrandi (Box 109)
      - Villa Borghese (Box 109)
        - Exterior (Box 109)
        - Interior (Box 109)
      - Villa Chigi (Box 109)
      - Villa Doria-Pamphili (Box 109)
      - Villa Farnesina (Box 109)
      - Villa Giulia (Box 109–110)
      - Villa Ludoviso-Bon Compagni (Box 110)
      - Villa Madama (Box 110)
        - Exterior (Box 110)
        - Interior, interior detail (Box 110)
      - Villa Medici (Box 110)
        - Exterior (Box 110)
        - Gardens (Box 110)
      - Villa Montalito (Box 110)
      - Villa Farnesiana (Box 110)
      - Villa Oce Pigneto (Box 110)
      - Villa Savelli Paretti (Box 110)
  - Sabbioneta (Box 110)
  - S. Benedetta Po (Box 110)
  - S. Giovanni Valdarno (Box 110)
  - S. Gregorio da Sassola (Box 110)
  - S. Gimignano (Box 110)
  - S. Leo (Pasaro-Urbino) (Box 110)
  - S. Miniato al Tedesco (Box 111)
  - Santa Sophia (Box 111)
  - Savona (Piedmont) (Box 111)
  - Sbanico (Box 111)
  - Siena (Box 111)
    - Churches (Box 111)
      - Cathedral (Box 111)
        - Piccolimini Library (Box 111)
        - Pavements (Box 111)
      - Absalom (Box 111)
      - Liberation of Betulia (Box 111)
      - Masacre of Innocents (Box 111)
      - Sibyls (Box 111)
        - Chiesa Del'Ospedale (Box 111)
      - Fountains (Box 111)
      - Palaces (Box 111)
        - Palace Piccolomini (Box 111)
        - Palace Spannochi (Box 111)
      - Squares (Box 111)
  - Stra (Box 111)
  - Stupinigi (Box 111–112)
  - Syracuse (Box 112)
  - Tivoli (Box 112)
    - Villa d'Este (Box 112)
      - Exterior (Box 112)
      - Gardens (Box 112)
  - Todi (Box 112)
    - Churches (Box 112)
      - S. Maria Della Consolazione (Box 112)
  - Trino (Box 112)
  - Turin (Box 112)
    - Teatro Regio (Box 112)
    - Churches (Box 112)
      - Carthusian Monastery (Box 112)
      - Cathedral of Giovanni Battista (Box 112)
        - Exterior (Box 112)
        - Interior (Box 112)
      - S. Lorenzo (Box 112)
        - Exterior (Box 113)
        - Interior (Box 113)
      - Superga (Box 113)
    - Palaces (Box 113)
      - Castello del Valentino (Box 113)
      - Palazzo Carignano (Box 113)
      - Palazzo Madama (Box 113)
      - Palazzo Municipale (Box 113)
  - Urbino (Box 113)
    - Churches (Box 113)
      - S. Bernardino (Box 113)
    - Palaces (Box 113)
      - Palazzo Ducale (Box 113)
        - Exterior (Box 113)
        - Interior (Box 113)
          - Doors (Box 113–114)
  - Vallinotto (Box 114)
  - Velletri (Box 114)
  - Venice (Box 114)
    - Plans (Box 114)
    - Views (Box 114)
    - Bridges (Box 114)
      - Bridge of Sighs (Box 114)
      - Porte Di Riatto (Box 114)
    - Churches (Box 114)
      - Chiesa Dei Gesuita (Box 114)
      - Il Redentore (Box 114)
      - S. Francesco Della Vigna (Box 114)
      - S. Giobbe (Box 114)
      - S. Giorgio Dei Grecia (Box 114)
      - S. Giorgio Maggiore (Box 114)
        - Exterior (Box 114)
        - Interior (Box 114)
      - S. Giovanni e Paolo (Box 114)
      - S. Marco (Box 114)
      - S. Maria dei Miracoli (Box 114–115)
      - S. Maria Della Salute (Box 115)
        - Exterior (Box 115)
        - Interior (Box 115)
      - S. Maria Formosa (Box 115)
      - S. Maria Dei Giglio (Box 115)
      - S. Moise (Box 115)
      - S. Nicolo Del Tolentino (Box 115)
      - S. Pietro di Castelo (Box 115)
      - S. Rocco (Box 115)
      - S. Salvatore (Box 115)
      - Church Degli Scalzi (Box 115)
      - S. Simone Piccolo (Box 115)
      - S. Stae (Box 115)
      - S. Zaccaria (Box 115)
    - Columns (Box 115)
    - Government Buildings (Box 115)
    - Libraries (Box 115)
      - Libreria di S. Marco (Box 115)
    - Museums (Box 115)
    - Palaces (Box 115)
      - Palazzo Corner della Ca'Grande (Box 115)
      - Palazzo Corner-Spineli (Box 115)
      - Palazzo Cornaro A S. Polo (Box 115)
      - Palazzo Ducale (Box 115)
        - Courtyard and Giant's Staircase (Box 115)
        - Interior (Box 115)
        - Interior Colums (Box 115)
      - Palazzo Grimani (Box 115)
      - Palazzo Minelli (Box 116)
      - Palazzo Morosini (Box 116)
      - Palazzo Papadopoli (Box 116)
      - Palazzo Pesaro (Box 116)
      - Palazzo Vendramin-Calergi (Box 116)
      - Palazzo Widmann (Box 116)
    - Schools (Box 116)
      - Scuola Di S. Giogio (Box 116)
      - Scuola Di S. Marco (Box 116)
    - Squares (Box 116)
      - Piazza Di S. Marco (Box 116)
        - Plans (Box 116)
        - Views (Box 116)
          - Clock Tower (Box 116)
          - Campanile & Logetta (Box 116)
          - Piazzetta (Box 116)
  - Verona (Box 116)
    - Churches (Box 116)
      - Madona Si Campagna (Box 116)
      - S. Giogio in Braida (Box 116)
      - S. Maria in Organo (Box 116)
    - Gates (Box 116)
      - Porta Nuova (Box 116)
      - Porta Palino (Box 116)
      - Porta Di Santo Zeno (Box 117)
    - Hospitals (Box 117)
    - Palaces (Box 117)
      - Palazzo Belvilaquea (Box 117)
      - Palazzo Canossa (Box 117)
      - Palazzo Degli Honorji (Box 117)
      - Palazzo Del Consiglio (Box 117)
      - Palazzo Della Gran Guardi Vecchia (Box 117)
      - Palazzo Giusti (Box 117)
      - Palazzo Maffei (Box 117)
      - Palazzo Pompeii Alla Vittoria (Box 117)
  - Vicenza (Box 117)
    - Palaces (Box 117)
      - Palazzo Barbarano (Box 117)
      - Palazzo Chiericati (Museo Civico) (Box 117)
      - Palazzo Del Liceo Pigafetta (Box 117)
      - Palazzo Ragione (Basilica) (Box 117–118)
      - Palazzo Thiene (Box 118)
      - Palazzo Tressing Dal Velo D'Oro (Box 118)
      - Palazzo Valmarana (Box 118)
    - Theaters (Box 118)
      - Teatro Olimpico (Box 118)
    - Villas (Box 118)
      - Villa Capra (Rotunda) (Box 118)
        - Exterior (Box 118)
        - Interior (Box 118)
      - Villa Cordellina (Box 118)
  - Vigevano (Box 118)
  - Viterbo (Box 118)
  - Volterra (Box 118)
  - Zara (Box 118)
- Malta (Box 118)
  - Valetta (Box 118)
- Poland (Box 118)
  - Thorn (Box 118)
  - Krakov (Box 118)
- Portugal (Box 118)
  - Azeito (Box 118)
  - Belem (Box 118)
  - Braga (Box 118)
  - Coimbra (Box 119)
  - Euora (Box 119)
  - Lisbon (Box 119)
  - Macao, China (Box 119)
  - Mafra (Box 119)
  - Milagres (Box 119)
  - Oporto (Box 119)
  - Queluz (Box 119)
  - Setubal (Box 119)
  - Thomar (Box 119)
- Rumania (Box 119)
  - Various (Box 119)
- Russia (Box 119)
  - General (Box 119)
  - Dyakovo (Box 119)
  - Fili (Box 119)
  - Istra (Box 119)
  - Kiev (Box 119)
  - Kizhi (Box 119)
  - Kolomenskoe (Box 119)
  - Kondopoga (Box 119)
  - Kozeletsk (Box 119)
  - Lake Valdai (Box 119)
  - Leningrad (Box 119)
    - Banks (Box 119)
    - Churches (Box 120)
      - Trinity Cathedral (Box 120)
    - Government Buildings (Box 120)
      - Admiralty (Box 120)
      - Arsenal (Box 120)
    - Houses (Box 120)
    - Palaces (Box 120)
      - Hermitage & Winter Palace (Box 120)
      - Peterhof (Box 120)
    - Schools (Box 120)
    - Theaters (Box 120)
  - Mogilev (Box 120)
  - Moscow (Box 121)
    - Churches (Box 121)
      - Basilius Cathedral (Box 121)
      - Novo Devici Monastery (Box 121)
    - Kremlin (Box 121)
      - Churches (Box 121)
        - Cathedral of Archangel Michael (Box 121)
        - Cathedral of the Assumption (Box 121)
  - Nekolskoe (Box 121)
  - Nenoksa (Box 121)
  - Nizhni (Box 121)
  - Novgorod (Box 121)
  - Ostankino (Box 121)
  - Ostrov (Box 121)
  - Panilovo (Box 121)
  - Pavlovsk (Box 121)
  - Pell (Box 121)
  - Rostov-the Great (Box 122)
  - Rostovskoe Village (Box 122)
  - Staraya Ladoga (Box 122)
  - Tikbinski (Box 122)
  - Torjhka (Box 122)
  - Tsaritsin (now Lenino, Stalingrad) (Box 122)
  - Tsarkoe Seloe (Box 122)
  - Tsivozero (Box 122)
  - Varzaug (Box 122)
  - Yadrovo (Box 122)
  - Yalta (Box 122)
  - Yaroslavl (Box 122)
  - Zagorsk (Box 122)
  - Zavadovski Palace (Box 122)
  - Zvenigorod (Box 122)
- Spain (Box 122)
  - General (Box 122)
  - Architects (Box 122)
  - Cities (Box 122)
    - Alcala de Henares (Box 122)
      - Achiepiscopal Palace (Box 122)
      - University (Box 122)
  - Alcaraz (Box 122)
  - Aranjuez (Box 122)
  - Arcos de la Frontera (Box 122)
  - Astorga (Box 122)
  - Avila (Box 122–123)
  - Azpeitia (Box 123)
  - Barcelona (Box 123)
  - Burgos (Box 123)
    - Cathedral (Box 123)
  - Cadiz (Box 123)
    - Cathedral (Box 123)
      - Interior (Box 123)
    - Church Our Lady of Carmen (Box 123)
  - Carmona (Box 123)
  - Cogolludo (Box 123)
  - Cordova (Box 123)
    - Churches (Box 123)
      - Cathedral (Box 123)
      - Convento de la Merced (Box 123)
      - S. Pedro (Box 123)
  - Coria (Caceres) (Box 123)
  - Ecija (Box 123)
  - El Pardo (Box 123)
  - El Paular (Box 123)
  - Escorial (Box 123)
    - Original Herrera Designs (Box 123–124)
    - Distant Views (Box 124)
    - Exterior (Box 124)
      - South Façade (Box 124)
    - Interior (Box 124–125)
      - Various (Box 125)
      - Casita de Arriba (Box 125)
      - Church of S. Lorenzo (Box 125)
      - Galeria Convalecientes (Box 125)
      - Gardens (Box 125)
      - Patio de los Evangelista (Box 125)
      - Patio of the Mascarones (Box 125)
      - Patio de la Portena (Box 125)
      - Small Palace Courtyard (Box 125)
  - Escorial de Abajo (Box 125)
  - Estepa (Box 125)
  - Fernan Nunez (Box 125)
  - Granada (Box 125)
    - Churches (Box 125)
      - Cartuja (Box 125)
      - Cathedral (Box 125)
      - Palaces (Box 125–126)
  - Guadulupe (Box 126)
  - Guadalajara (Box 126)
  - Guadix (Box 126)
  - Jaen (Box 126)
  - Jerez de la Frontera (Box 126)
    - Churches (Box 126)
      - Carthusian Church (Box 126)
      - Collegiate Church (Box 126)
  - La Granja (Box 126)
  - La Vid (Box 126)
  - Leon (Box 126)
    - Museum (Box 126)
  - Liria (Box 126)
  - Loeches (Box 126)
  - Lorca (Box 126)
  - Loro Del Rio (Box 126)
  - Loyola (Box 126)
  - Lucena (Box 126)
  - Lupiana (Box 126)
  - Madrid (Box 126)
    - Churches (Box 126)
      - Descalzas Reales (Box 126)
      - Ermita de la Virgen del Puerto (Box 126)
    - Museums (Box 126)
    - Palaces (Box 126)
      - Royal Palace (Box 127)
  - Malaga (Box 127)
  - Medina de Rio Seco (Box 127)
  - Mota del Marquez (Box 127)
  - Mues (Box 127)
  - Murcia (Box 127)
  - Nuevo Baztan (Box 127)
  - Osuna (Box 127)
  - Palma (Box 127)